The city's humming, the lights are low I'm
waiting for you, I'm ready to go The rain is
tapping on the glass I knew this feeling would
fail to last I hear your footsteps in the hall I'm
not afraid to fall This is the only thing I know is
true You've got my neon heart Shining for you in
the dark A love so bright it's all but yours
You've got my neon heart It's an electric color
feeling And it all starts with you
We're walking fast on the wet concrete The
rhythm matches when our eyes meet Don't need a
promise, don't need a vow My only moment is right
here, right now I hear your footsteps in the hall
I'm not afraid to fall This is the only thing I
know is true You've got my neon heart Shining for
you in the dark A love so bright it's off the
charts You've got my neon heart It's an electric
color feeling And it all starts with you
A chance that we're both gonna take You've
got my neon heart shining, shining for you In the
dark, a love so bright, it's off the charts
You've got my neon heart, it's an electric color
feeling And it all starts with you, you Money on
heart.
Money on heart.